(Bernadette:)We're here today
to celebrate love.
(Alfred:)Sigh louder,
no one heard you.
(Stuart:)Really, I can move.
(Bernadette:)Not just Leonard and
Penny's love, but the love
(Bernadette:)we have for them,
as well as each other.
(Sheldon:)Speaking of love, STDs among
the elderly are skyrocketing.
(Bernadette:)Love is patient,
but it's not gonna put up
(Bernadette:)with all the side chatter,
so let's knock it off!
(Howard:)At least she's yelling at
someone else for a change.
Howard!
(Penny:)Okay, I understand everyone's
a little tense today,
(Penny:)so I am just gonna get
to the important stuff.
(Penny:)Leonard, standing here
with you in front
(Penny:)of our family and friends is
bringing up a lot of feelings.
(Penny:)Like what a good idea it was
to elope the first time.